【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
怎么样? 乔伊的家
Huh? So, what do you think? Casa de Joey.
我自己装修的      少来了
I decorated it myself.        Get out. No.
乔伊 这真是...
Wow, Joey, this is, uh...
艺术      没错是艺术
Art.        Art it is.
看看这个 这是咖啡桌吗?
Well, check this out. Is it a coffee table?
还是一只美洲豹? 无所谓了
Is it, uh, a panther? There's no need to decide.
好漂亮的枕头
Hey, nice pillow.
这真的是布偶皮么?
So tell me, is this genuine Muppet skin?
嘿 好极了 流水的东西
Hey, excellent. Excellent watertable thing.
谢谢 我也喜欢这个 但是你知道么?
Thanks. I love this. But you know what?
它会让我想尿尿
It makes me want to pee.
对 我也是 我想这就是挑战所在
Yeah, me too. I think that's the challenge. Heh.
钱德怎么没来呢?
Hey, how come, uh, Chandler didn't come?
因为他有事 就是有事
Well, uh, it's because he had a thing with the...with the thing.
哦 我懂了
Right. I got it.
带我们去看看你家的其他部分吧
Why don't you show us the rest of your casa?
是啊      哦哦 最棒的部分 跟我来
Yeah.        Uh, oh, oh, the best part. Come on.
看?
Huh?
嘿
Hey.
好棒的马桶
Nice toilet.
不不不 后面那个
No, no, no. Behind it.
你厕所也装电话?      是的
You have a phone in here?        That's right.
我装了个电话
I have a phone.
在这里
In here.
乔伊 答应我一件事      什么?
Joey, promise me something.        Yeah.
别用那个电话打给我
Never call me from that phone.
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第17集
艾迪搬进来了 The One Where Eddie Moves In
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
好了 来了
Okay, here we go.
亲 抱歉 苹果派卖完了 某人刚拿走了最后一块
Honey, I'm sorry, they were all out of apple pie. Someone just got the last piece.
天呐 你们不会相信的
Oh my God. Oh, my God. You are not gonna believe this.
我刚刚被发现了
I have just been discovered.
等等 四年前我就宣布你是法国领地了
Now wait a minute. I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.
总之 好了
Anyway.Okay
现在你们要保证不会发狂也别说多棒 直到我说完
Now promise you won't freak out and say how great this is until I'm done.
好      好
Okay.        Okay.
我刚认识了一个小唱片公司的制作人
Uh, I just met this producer of this teeny record company...
她说我有一副清新 与众不同的嗓音
who said, ahem, that I have a very fresh, off beat sound...
她想请我录"臭臭猫"的试听带
and she wants to do a demo of "Smelly Cat".
我刚说过别这样
Okay, I told you not to do that yet. Ha ha.
好
Okay.
她还要拍MTV
And she wants to do a video.
我还没说完呢
I'm not done yet, okay? Ha, ha.
天啊
God. Okay.
如果一切顺利 他们甚至可能出一张专辑
If that goes well, they may even want to make an album.
我说完了      太棒了!
I'm done now.        Oh, that's great.
难以置信
That's unbelievable. Oh.
罗斯 如果你关心我
Oh, God, Ross, if you care about me,
就把派从那人的帽子里拿出来
get the pie out of the man's hood.
拿什么?      他帽子里有块派
Get the what?        There's a pie in the hood.
派在帽子里 快去
Pie in the hood. Go.
你在干嘛?      对不起 我的派在你的帽子里
What are you doing?        I'm sorry. My pie was, was in your hood.
我得从那家伙的裤子里拿我的咖啡了
Now I just have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants...
然后七点前我要回医院去
and I'll be back in the hospital by seven.
可恶 罗斯 赶快给我滚出来
Damn it, Ross. Get your butt out of the bathroom.
淡定 我在吹头发
Calm down. I'm blow drying.
吹什么头发? 你根本没有头发
Blow drying what? You have no hair.
怎么了?      你男朋友在里面待了一个小时
What's going on?        Uh, your boyfriend has been in there for an hour.
真不敢相信 就像我又跟他住在一起了一样
It's like I'm living with him again.
我睡觉时他在这儿 醒来时他在
He's here when I go to sleep, he's here when I wake up,
我要洗澡时他还在
he's here when I wanna use the shower.
感觉好像我又回到十六岁了
Uh, I feel like I'm 16 over again.
你不是十六岁 而且现在你们两个都是成年人了
Well, you're not 16. You're both adults now.
快出来 蠢货
Get out, you doofus!
其实 你们俩半斤八两
Or, you know, he's rubber and you're glue.
都是你的了
All yours.
希望你把排水孔上的头发清理了
I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.
闭嘴!      闭嘴
Shut up.        Shut up.
别这样
Cut it out.
我再也不想要你了
I've never wanted you more.
怎么样? 我该不该打电话给他?
So, what do you say, boys? Should I call him?
大家都是这样说的 "问你拖鞋一个问题"
You know what they say "Ask your slippers a question..."
你疯了!"
you're going crazy.
你好      嘿
Hello?        Hey.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉 我今天没过去
Listen, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
因为你有事嘛
You, uh, you had a thing.
听说你那里很棒      别提了 我开心死了
Yeah, well, I hear the place looks great.        Oh, forget about it. I'm having a ball, ha.
我们的公寓怎么样了?
How's the apartment doing?
哦 棒极了 就是一个普通的空间
Oh. Hey, it's terrific. I mean, it's a regular space...
的聚集地
fest.
那很好
Oh, well, great.
我只是打来打声招呼
Yeah, I just...wanted to call and say hey.
好的
Well, okay, then.
那是烤箱计时器的声音吗?      没错 朋友
Was that the oven timer?        That's right, my friend.
是看"海滩游侠"的时候了      海滩游侠!
It's time for Baywatch!        Baywatch!
哦
Oh.
你能相信他们让史黛芬妮得皮肤癌么?
Can you believe they gave Stephanie skin cancer?
我还是不敢相信他们升她为小队长
I still can't believe they promoted her to lieutenant.
你那么说是因为你喜欢雅丝敏布莉
You're just saying that because you're in love with Yasmine Bleeth.
怎么可能有人不喜欢雅丝敏布莉?
How could anyone not be in love with Yasmine Bleeth?
嘿 她们在跑了
Hey. Hey, they're running.
看 这正是这个节目的精华所在
See, this is the brilliance of the show.
我说她们应该一直跑下去
I say always keep them running.
一直在跑
All the time running.
跑吧!
Run.
跑啊 雅丝敏 像风一样的跑
Run. Yasmine. Run like the wind.
但你说想一个人住的
But you wanted to live by yourself.
是啊 我还以为那样会很好
I did. I thought it'd be great.
我以为那样我就有时间思考
I figured I'd have time alone with my thoughts.
但结果发现我的思想没有你们想的那么多
But you know, it turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you'd think.
乔伊 那怎么不和钱德说你想搬回去?
Joey, why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?
你们真觉得他会答应么? 昨晚我们聊得很好
You really think he'd take me? I mean, we had a good talk last night.
但是当初我搬出去时我伤他很深
But when I moved out, I hurt him bad.
我保证 他绝对想要你搬回去
I promise you, he would definitely want you back.
我告诉你 他绝对不会搬回来
I'm telling you, there's no way he's moving back.
但我们从没像昨晚那样聊的那么开心过
But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night. Heh.
那就好像
I mean it was
就像我们刚刚搬在一起住时一样
It was like when we first started living together.
我知道你现在不想听这个
Look, I know you don't want to hear this right now.
但我们看到他在新家的样子 他真的很开心
but we've seen him in his new place. All right, and he's happy.
他都装修好了
He's, he's decorated.
钱德 他已经往前走了 你也要这样      但是
Look, Chandler, he has moved on, okay? You have to, too.        But
你只是要接受你们现在只是朋友的事实 好么?
No, you're just gonna have to accept the fact that you're just friends now. Okay?
你们不再是
You're not...
室友了
roommates anymore.
好了 菲比 准备好了吗?
Okay, Phoebe. Ready to try one?
好的
Okay. Ahem.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么?
What are they feeding you?
臭臭猫 臭臭猫 真的很臭的臭臭猫
Smelly, smelly, smelly. Really bad smelling smelly cat.
哇 天啊
Oh, whoa! Oh, my God!
那是谁啊?
I mean, like, who was that?
她们是你的伴唱团 就在你后面 亲爱的
They're your backup singers. Behind you, hon.
我以为她们只是来参观的
Oh, I thought they were just watching me.
就像水族馆一样      好了
Like at an aquarium, you know?        All right.
从头开始      好的
From the top.        Okay. Ahem.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么?
What are they feeding you?
臭臭 臭臭
Smelly, smelly, smelly
非常臭的臭臭猫
Really bad smelling smelly cat
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
对不起 我没有感觉到
Okay, sorry. I'm just not getting...
大家都懂 这只猫到底有多臭
that everyone, urn, gets how smelly this cat actually is.
或许我们可以聊一下这个
I think maybe if we could talk about this...
因为我需要感觉到你们真的在乎这只猫
because I need to feel that you really care about the cat.
亲爱的 我们可以谈 但这儿一分钟要花一百刀
Honey, we can talk about this. It's just that it's costing about $100 a minute to be in here.
好吧 那猫是很臭 不过你们还是爱他 开始吧
Oh, okay. So, urn, the cat stinks, but you love it. Let's go.
不 他不可能是迅猛龙
No, there is no way he was a velociraptor.
不 看他高耸的头盖骨
No, look at the cranial ridge, okay?
要是狄诺是迅猛龙
If Dino was a velociraptor,
他一口就把摩登原始人一家吃掉了
he'd have eaten the Flintstones.
没错
Yeah. Yeah.
噢 你在睡午觉?
Oh, were you taking a nap?
本来是      噢 我
I was.        Oh I, oh,
等等 东尼 请你等下 我有电话进来
wait, Tony, can you hold on? That's the other line.
喂?
Hello?
是的 她在 但可以请她回电吗?
Yeah, she's here, but, uh, can she call you back?
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
回电话给乔安娜      她留电话号码了么?
Call Joanna. Hi.        Did she leave a number?
你看见我写下来了么?
Did you see me write one down?
我没有她电话号码 笨蛋
I don't have her number. Butt munch.
那她会再打回来的 别这么幼稚
Well, she'll call back. Don't be such a baby.
我不幼稚 你才幼稚
I'm not a baby. You're the baby.
听着 你别烦我好么?      你别惹我好么
Look, you wanna get off my back?        You wanna get out of my face?
等一下 东尼 等一下
Wait, hold on, Tony. Hold on.
你好?
Hello?
你好
Hi.
是的 没有 她就在这 等等
Yeah, no, she's right here. Urn, hold on.
东尼 我再打回给你 我妹妹的男朋友打来了
Hi, Tony, can I call you back? That's, uh, that's my sister's boyfriend.
给我      好
Give me that.        Okay.
亲爱的 听着 趁我还没忘
Hi sweetie, listen, before I forget,
我的避孕器是不是留在你那儿了?
did I leave my diaphragm at your place?
嗨 妈
Hi Mom.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Yeah. ha ha.
皇宫生活怎么样?
So, uh, how's the palace?
真有趣你居然会提到 因为我刚在想
It's funny you should mention that because I was thinking...
这些盒子是怎么回事?
What's with the boxes?
噢 事实上 我有个消息要告诉你
Oh, uh, actually, I, uh, have some news.
乔伊会回来把他的麋鹿帽子拿走
Hey Chandler, is that Joey guy gonna pick up his moose hat
还是要我把它扔了?
or should I toss it out?
你为何不亲自问他呢?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
乔伊 这位是我的新室友 艾迪
Joey, this is my new roommate, Eddie.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我也是      你好么
Like wise.        How you doing?
我带走了 我就是为了这个来的
Uh, I'll take that. It's, uh, what I came for, heh.
这倒是个新闻 你们俩怎么认识的?
So this is new. Where'd you two meet?
在超市 在民族食品区
At the, uh, supermarket in the, uh, ethnicfood section.
我帮他选西班牙辣香肠      哇奥
I helped him pick out a chorizo. Yeah. Hahaha.      Wow.
后来我们聊了一下
Oh you know, we got to talking. And, uh,
他说要找地方住 我刚好有空房间
he said he needed a place, and I had a spare room.
哦 那是一个空房间了?
Oh, now it's a spare room?
是啊 既然没有人在用
Well, yeah. In that it's not being used...
我又让它空着
and I have it to spare.
对的
Right.
好了 我拿到我来拿的东西了
Well, I, uh, got what I came for.
再见了
I'll, uh, I'll see you guys.
嘿 乔伊
Hey, Joe.
你什么时候开始在头发上抹慕丝的?
When'd you start using moose in your hair?
这家伙很有趣吧?
Is this guy great, or what?
对啊
Yeah.
很有趣
Yeah, he is.
我不敢相信他找到新室友了 这人是谁?
I can't believe he has a new roommate. Who is this guy?
艾迪什么的 他们刚认识
Uh, Eddie something. He just met him.
这关系不会持久的
It'll never last.
他不过是低潮时填补空档的室友
He's just a rebound roommate.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
快看 快看
Oh, check it out. Oh, check it out.
是"臭臭猫"的MTV      天啊
It's "Smelly Cat", the video.        Oh, God.
我还没看 所以要是你们不喜欢的话
Now, okay, I haven't seen it yet, so if you don't like it.
那又怎样? 你们也没人录过MTV
Well, so what? None of you ever made a video.
好的
Okay.
"臭臭猫" 菲比布非
"Smelly Cat" Phoebe Buffay
快滚出去 猫 你臭死了
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
美极了      看看我
Oh, smoking.        Oh, look at me.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么?
What are they feeding you?
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
臭臭 臭臭 真的很臭 臭臭猫 这不是你的错
Smelly, smelly, smelly. Really bad smelling smelly cat. It's not your fault.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
天啊      我知道
Oh, my God!        I know.
我的声音真美
I sound amazing!
他们不带你去看兽医 显然你不是他们的最爱
They won't take you to the vet. You're obviously not their favorite pet.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
哦不
Oh, no
我以前从没听过自己的唱歌 除了在我自己脑袋里
I've never heard myself sing before. I mean, except in my own head. Oh.
真酷 我现在可以听到你们听到的声音了
This is so cool. Now I can hear what you hear.
相当不同 对吧?
Pretty, uh, different, huh?
哦对不起 但我真是太有才了
Oh, I am sorry, but I'm incredibly talented.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
乔伊 怎么了?
Hey, Joey. What's going on, man?
艾迪
Eddie.
早      早
Morning.        Morning.
我来拿我的信
I just, uh, came by to pick up my mail.
信在哪里?      在那边桌上
Where's the mail?        Oh it's, uh, over there on the table.
你们不再放在这边桌子上了吗?
You don't keep it on this table anymore?
不 艾迪习惯把信放那边
No, Eddie likes it over there.
好吧 给你 艾迪式煎蛋
All right, here you go, my friend. Eggs a Ia Eddie, huh.
哦哦
Ooh. Ooh.
太棒了
Oh, oh. That's great.
怎么了?
What?
我还以为你喜欢我做的面包挖个洞 中间放蛋呢
No, I just thought you liked your eggs, with the bread with the hole in the middle. a Ia me.
我是喜欢 但艾迪的做法是这样 还挺好吃的
I do, but, uh, Eddie makes them this way. They're pretty darn good.
好了 大家
Well, you guys...
我走了
I'm out of here.
再见了      再见
See you, pals.        See you.
你们两个相处得怎么样?      再开心不过了
So how are you two getting along?        Oh, I couldn't be happier.
很好
Great, huh?
我为你感到高兴
I'm happy for you.
好了 我受够了
All right, that's it!
他就这样住进来 这位强尼新蛋蛋先生
He just comes in here, Mr Johnny New Eggs.
换了放信的地方 还有那"再见了 大家"
with his moving the mail and his "See you, pals."
果汁也没了
And now there's no juice!
没留果汁给想喝果汁的人 我想喝果汁 我需要果汁
There's no juice for the people who need the juice. I want the juice. I need the juice!
那边还有一盒
There's another carton right over there.
这不再是果汁的问题了 好么?
Hey, this isn't about juice anymore, all right, man?
好吧 那是为了什么?      蛋
All right. So, what's it about?        Eggs.
谁的蛋你比较喜欢 他的还是我的?
Whose eggs do you like better, his or mine, huh?
两个人的蛋我都喜欢      拜托
Well, I like both eggs equally.        Oh, come on!
没有人会喜欢两种蛋一样多的
Nobody likes two different kinds of eggs equally.
你更喜欢哪一种? 我要知道答案
You like one better than the other and I wanna know which.
有区别么? 你的蛋现在又不在这里了 不是么
What's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore, are they?
你带走了你的蛋 然后离开了!
You took your eggs, and you left!
你真想希望我再也找不到新蛋了么?
Did you really expect me to never find new eggs?
我晚上想看今夜娱乐
I wanna watch Entertainment Tonight.
不要 我们要看赛伦盖提的掠食者
Tough. We're watching Predators of the Serengeti.
你们两个别争了好么?
Would you guys stop?
这是我的电视!      什么?
It's my TV!        What?
住手      咬我啊
Quit it.        Bite me!
天啊
Oh, my God.
摩妮卡一直在转台
Well, Monica keeps changing the channel.
真棒 你怎么不跟妈妈告状去啊
Aw, that's great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
现在我变成过家家里的妈妈了
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
听着 我拒绝被卷入你们
Look, I refuse to get sucked into
这一类诡异的盖勒家庭纠纷里
this weird little Geller dimension thing, okay?
所以我要去好好泡个泡泡浴
So I'm gonna go take a nice long hot bubble bath...
因为你们两个孩子吵得我快疯了
because you kids are driving me crazy
我们该怎么办?
What do we do about this?
我想我们可以把今夜娱乐录下来
I guess we could tape Entertainment Tonight.
我不是说电视节目
Not that!
这个! 我们!
This! Us!
天啊 罗斯 你真的是
Oh, my God, Ross, it's, you're just...
自从你来这里以后 我快被你逼疯了...      哦哦
Since you've been here, you're driving...        Ow, ow.
摩妮卡 你又开始高八度了
Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, all right?
我真是不能忍受你在这儿
I just can't stand you being here...
总是在这儿
all the time!
为什么? 你为什么受不了我在这儿?
Why? Why can't you stand me being here?
我们只是在闹着玩而已
We're just having fun.
玩? 你觉得这好玩么?
Fun? You think this is fun?
是的
Yeah.
拜托 我还以为我们在闹着玩 就像小时候那样
Come on, I mean I thought you know, I thought we were fooling around, like when, uh, when we were kids.
罗斯 小时候我恨你
Ross, I hated you when we were kids.
小时候你恨我?      是的 我恨你
You hated me when we were kids?        Yes. I hated you.
我爱你就像"你是我哥 我只能这样"
I mean, I loved you in a "you're my brother so I have to" way.
但基本上我是恨你的
But basically, I hated your guts.
你干嘛要恨我?      因为你对我很刻薄
Why did you hate me?        Because you were mean to me...
你嘲弄我 你总是得逞
and you teased me and you always, you always got your way.
你不觉得那好玩?
And that wasn't fun for you?
啊哈
Uhhuh.
我不敢相信你恨我
I can't believe you hated me.
但现在我爱你啊
But now I love you.
而且不是因为我必须这样     真的吗?
And not just because I have to.        Really?
是的
Yeah.
你只是必须停止再惹我了
You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.
这我办得到
I can do that.
那我就不用杀掉你了
Then I won't have to kill you.
那你想看今夜娱乐么?
So you wanna watch, uh, Entertainment Tonight?
是的 谢了
Yeah, thanks.
今晚 美国运动杂志要
Tonight, America's premier sports magazine moves to primetime...
你知道么?      嗯?
You know what?        What?
要是你真的想看那个
If you really wanna watch that
赛伦盖提草原什么的 我们可以看
Serengeti thing, we can.
哦 好的
Oh, okay.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
听着 你们一定不会相信
Listen, you are not going to believe this...
原来MTV里唱歌的人不是我
but, ahem, that is not me singing on the video.
不会吧
No.
没错
Yes.
你怎么发现的?
Well, how did you find out?
唱片公司把合同寄给我 要我签名同意
Well, okay, the record company sent over this piece of paper for me to sign saying that it's okay
让别人代唱 那是我第一个线索
for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.
那你要怎么办呢?
So, what are you gonna do?
我不能和这样做的人合作      当然
I can't work with people who would do this.        Sure.
这可怜的女人
I mean, this poor woman.
哪个女人?
What woman?
代唱的女人
The voice woman.
她的嗓音那么好 但她却没有MTV
I mean she has a great voice, but she doesn't have a video.
菲比 那你怎么办?
Okay, Pheebs, but what about you?
我有MTV 你们得注意听我说话
I have a video. You have to pay attention.
这个代唱的女人 她很有才华
No, this voice woman, she's so talented.
但据制作人说 她长的不够好看之类的
But according to the producer people, they said like she doesn't have the right look or something. You know?
她就像被人丢弃在水池里的小动物
She's like one of those animals at the pound...
只因为他们不够漂亮就没有人要
who nobody wants because they're not pretty enough.
或是一些老狗 因为太臭又
Or, you know, like some old dog who's kind of like stinky and, oh
天啊 她就是臭臭猫!
my God! She's smelly cat!
噢 这首歌真有深度
Oh, oh, that song has so many levels.
嘿 艾迪
Hey, Eddie.
要玩桌上足球吗?
You, uh, wanna play some foosball?
不要 谢了 我对运动不太有兴趣
No. thanks. man. I'm not, uh, not really into sports.
好的 没关系
Yeah, okay. All right.
没关系 看海滩游侠的时候到了
Doesn't matter. Time for Baywatch.
什么?
Oh what?
你喜欢那个秀?
You like that show?
你不喜欢那个秀?
You don't like that show?
什么? 不
Ha, ha, what? No.
不过是一群帅哥美女在海滩上跑来跑去
I mean, it's just pretty people running around on the beach.
这就是整个节目的精华所在啊
Well, that's the brilliance of it.
帅哥美女
The pretty people.
跑来跑去
And the running.
我要回房间看会书了
I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.
好吧
Oh, oh. Okay, man.
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们都喂你吃什么?
What are they feeding you?
大家一起唱!
Everybody!
臭臭猫 臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
摩妮卡!      他们不带你去兽医院
Monica.        They won't take you to the vet.
钱德!
Chandler.
你显然不是他们的最爱
You're obviously not their favorite pet.
乔伊!
Joey.
你或许不是玫瑰花床
You may not be a bed of roses.
瑞秋!      你不是有鼻子的人的朋友
Rachel        And you're no friend to those with noses.
罗斯 这首歌只有这几句 对不起 回到合唱!
Ross, those are the only lines we have. Sorry. Okay. Back to the chorus.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧